A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, Joseph E. Persico, Series 12 FA381
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Pre-Vice Presidential Speeches, 1966-1974; 3; 6.4 Cubic Feet
  - Council of Agricultural Organizations of New York State, Albany, New York, January 8, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 214)
  - Cafeteria Opening, Legislative Office Building, Albany, New York, January 9, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 215)
  - First Panel Sheriff's Jury Annual Dinner, New York City, January 11, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 216)
  - Farewell Dinner for Ambassador Rabin State of Israel Bonds, New York City, January 11, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 217)
  - Peter Brennan Reception, New York City, January 12, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 218)
  - Budget School, Albany, January 14, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 219)
  - New York Press Club, New York City, January 17, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 220)
  - News Conference, Albany, January 22, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 221)
  - New York State Veterans of Foreign War Legislative Dinner, Albany, New York, January 22, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 222)
  - News Conference, Albany, New York, January 23, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 223)
  - Annual Dinner of the Westchester Republican County Commission, New York City, January 25, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 224)
  - American Legion Legislative Dinner, Albany, New York, January 29, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 225)
  - Testimony of NAR before Joint Hearing of Senate and Assembly Codes Commission, Albany, New York, January 30, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 226)
  - Remarks of NAR at New York State Legislative Forum, Albany, New York, February 6, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 227)
  - Association of Towns Luncheon, New York City, February 6, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 228)
  - Drop-In at Association of Fire Districts Meeting, New York City, February 6, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 229)
  - Empire State Chamber of Commerce Dinner, Albany, New York, February 6, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 230)
  - Press Questions Lincoln Day Dinner, Chicago, Illinois, February 9, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 231)
  - Signing No-Fault Automobile Insurance Bill, Albany, New York, February 13, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 232)
  - Testimony of NAR U. S. Senate Subcommittee on Constitutional Rights, Washington, D. C., February 22, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 233)
  - Joint Session West Virginia State Legislature, Charleston, West Virginia, February 22, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 234)
  - State Council of Churches, Albany, New York, February 26, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 235)
  - New York State Publishers Association, Albany, New York, February 26, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 236)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Legislative Conference, Albany, New York, March 5, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 237)
  - Republican State Committee Meeting, Albany, New York, March 6, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 238)
  - New York State Broadcaster Association, Albany, New York, March 6, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 239)
  - Riverbank State Park Ceremony, New York City, March 9, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 240)
  - League of Women Voters, Albany, New York, March 6, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 241)
  - Women's National Republican Club, New York City, March 10, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 242)
  - Legislative Correspondence Association Dinner, Albany, New York, March 10, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 243)
  - Distinguished Service Awards Ceremony 25th Anniversary, State University, Albany, New York, March 13, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 244)
  - Impromptu Interview NAR, Capital, Albany, New York, March 13, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 245)
  - Governor Dunn Annual Prayer Breakfast, Nashville, Tennessee, March 22, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 246)
  - Press Conference of Robert Wagner on NBC-TV, New York City, March 22, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 247)
  - Opening Plenary Session of the Europe-America Conference by the International European Movement, Amsterdam, Netherlands, March 26, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 248)
  - Young Israel Annual Dinner, April 1, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 249)
  - Remarks of NAR Emma Willard School, Troy, New York, April 2, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 250)
  - World Trade Center, New York City, April 4, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 251)
  - Press Questions Prior to Remarks at the Commerce and Industry Lunch, New York City, April 4, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 252)
  - New York State Republican Committee Youth Conference, Albany, New York, April 9, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 253)
  - Press Conference of Governor Nelson Rockefeller at University Center, University of Montana, April 13, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 254)
  - New Haven Car Inaugural Ceremony, Stamford, Connecticut, April 16, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 255)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce Dinner, Norfolk, Virginia, April 18, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 256)
  - American Arbitration Association, New York City, April 19, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 257)
  - News Conference Red Room, State Capital, Albany, New York, April 26, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 258)
  - Four Freedoms Foundation Honoring Dr. Frank Stanton, New York City, April 26, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 259)
  - Society of Silurians, Americana Hotel, New York City, May 1, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 260)
  - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars on New Federalism, Washington, D. C., May 2, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 261)
  - University of Virginia Legal Forum, Charlottesville, Virginia, May 2, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 262)
  - Gold Medal Award to Dr. Ronan Citizens Budget Commission, New York City, May 3, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 263)
  - New York Urban League Annual Dinner Honoring Jackie Robinson, New York City, May 3, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 264)
  - Bill Signing Ceremony for Narcotics Bills, Red Room, Albany, New York, May 8, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 265)
  - Appointment of Michael Armstrong as District Attorney of Queens, New York City, May 9, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 266)
  - Kennedy Rail Link Bill Signing the Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, New York City, May 10, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 267)
  - Republican Governors Conference, New York, May 10, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 268)
  - News Conference, The Red Room, Albany, New York, May 14, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 269)
  - Press Conference at the White House, Washington, D. C., May 14, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 270)
  - Minutes of Meeting of National Study Commission on Water Pollution Control Policy, Washington, D. C., May 15, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 271)
  - Annual Award Presentations New York State Council of the Arts, New York City, May 17, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 272)
  - Award for Citizen Valor to Professor Francis H. Anderson, Albany, New York, May 21, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 273)
  - Press Questions Following Signing of Bill on the Adirondack Park, Albany, New York, May 22, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 274)
  - Presentation of the John LaFarge Memorial Award for Interracial Justice to Attorney General Louis J. Lefkowitz, Americana Hotel, New York City, May 24, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 275)
  - News Conference, Red Room, Albany, New York, May 25, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 276)
  - St. Lawrence University Commencement, Canton, New York, May 27, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 277)
  - Press Interview of NAR, Jewish National Fund Testimonial Dinner Honoring NAR and Mrs. Tom McCall, Portland, Oregon, June 4, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 278)
  - Executive Session National Governor's Conference, Lake Tahoe, Nevada, June 4, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 279)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Governor's Labor Reception, Americana Hotel, New York City, June 12, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 280)
  - Remarks of NAR at the New York State Republican Dinner, New York Hilton, New York City, June 13, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 281)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Annual State Committee Luncheon, New York Hilton, New York City, June 14, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 282)
  - Remarks of NAR at the New York Republican State Committee Dinner, Waldorf-Astoria, New York City, June 14, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 283)
  - Jack Flynn Testimonial 40 Second Tape, "New York Daily News," New York City, June 14, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 284)
  - Government Civic Center Dedication, Binghamton, New York, June 18, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 285)
  - Remarks of NAR at Summit County Republican Committee, Akron, Ohio, June 20, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 286)
  - United Jewish Appeal Luncheon, Essex House, New York, June 21, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 287)
  - Remarks of NAR at the New York State Broadcasters Association, Otesaga Hotel, Cooperstown, New York, July 17, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 288)
  - Press Briefing By Ron Maiorana, New York City, July 18, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 289)
  - Press Conference of NAR, New York City, July 18, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 290)
  - Press Conference of NAR, New York City, July 20, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 291)
  - Press Questions Following City Officials Meeting, New York City, July 24, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 292)
  - Staff Meeting Rockefeller Foundation, Time-Life Building, New York City, July 25, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 293)
  - Press Questions of NAR Following Briefing of Legislators on Transportation Bond Issue, Albany, New York, July 27, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 294)
  - Swearing in Ceremony of the New State Racing and Wagering Board, Hotel Gotham, New York City, August 7, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 295)
  - Press Questions and Answers Following Ceremony at Harlem River State Park, Bronx, New York, August 15, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 296)
  - American Political Science Association, Fairmont-Roosevelt Hotel, New Orleans, Louisiana, September 5, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 297)
  - Remarks of NAR at the New York State AFL-CIO Convention, Concord Hotel, New York, September 6, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 298)
  - Drug Law Interview of NAR on the "Today" Show, NBC-TV, New York City, September 7, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 299)
  - Swearing in of Judges, St. Regis Hotel, New York City, September 10, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 300)
  - NAR at News Conference, Biltmore Hotel, California, September 11, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 301)
  - Tape Interview of NAR and Roland D. Headlee, Biltmore Hotel, California, September 11, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 302)
  - Remarks of NAR at Town Hall of California, Biltmore Hotel, California, September 11, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 303)
  - Interview of NAR by David Burnham, "New York Times," New York City, September 12, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 304)
  - Press Conference of NAR and Congressman Charles W. Sandman, Latin Casino Theatre Restaurant, New Jersey, September 17, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 305)
  - NAR and Japanese Exchange Newsman, New York City, September 18, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 306)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Associated Industries Annual Dinner, Whiteface Inn, Lake Placid, New York, September 21, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 307)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Italian-American Legislators Dinner, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York City, September 21, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 308)
  - Remarks of NAR at Project Hope Awards Dinner Honoring Henry A. Kissinger, Plaza Hotel, New York City, September 25, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 309)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Executive Club Luncheon, Pick-Congress Hotel, Chicago, Illinois, September 28, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 310)
  - NAR at Meeting with Students at Pick-Congress Hotel, Chicago, Illinois, September 28, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 311)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Oakland County Republican Republican Committee, Bloomfield Hills, Michigan, September 29, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 312)
  - TV Taping of NAR on the Lou Grodon TV Show, Southfield, Michigan, September 29, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 313)
  - Macomb County Republican Club Annual Dinner, Hillcrest Country Club, Mt. Clemons, Michigan, September 29, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 314)
  - Press Questions of NAR at the Oakland-Pontiac Airport, Pontiac, Michigan, September 29, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 315)
  - United Fund Meeting, Manufacturers Hanover Trust Co., New York City, October 1, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 316)
  - Remarks of NAR at Fund Raising Event for John Marchi, New York City, October 1, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 317)
  - Cleveland Morning Exchange TV Program, Cleveland, Ohio, October 3, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 318)
  - Extemporaneous Remarks of NAR Delivered at the 46th Annual Conference of The Water Control Federation, Cleveland, Ohio, October 3, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 319)
  - Press Conference of NAR at the Cleveland Convention Center, Cleveland, Ohio, October 3, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 320)
  - TV Interview of NAR by Donald Fuldheim, Channel 5, Cleveland, Ohio, October 3, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 321)
  - Columbus Citizens Committee Annual Dinner, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York City, October 6, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 322)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Long Island Association Breakfast, East Meadow, New York, October 9, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 323)
  - Press Conference of NAR at 22 West 55th Street, New York City, October 10, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 324)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, Pacem In Terris III, Washington, D. C., October 11, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 325)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Westchester County Republican Committees Unity Reception, Westchester Country Club, Rye, New York, October 12, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 326)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Dedication Ceremony of the Northern Westchester Hospital Center, Mt. Kisco, New York, October 13, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 327)
  - NAR at the Cabinet Meeting, Red Room, The Capital, Albany, New York, October 16, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 328)
  - The Jewish Theological Seminary Inauguration Ceremony, New York City, October 21, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 329)
  - New York State United Nations Day Observance at Rockefeller Center, New York City, October 23, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 330)
  - New York Radio Market Broadcasters, Rockefeller Plaza, New York City, October 23, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 331)
  - Skylab I Presentation, New York City, October 23, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 332)
  - Press Conference at Phoenix Press Club, Phoenix, Arizona, October 25, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 333)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Phoenix Trunk 'n Tusk Dinner, Phoenix, Arizona, October 25, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 334)
  - College of Law, Arizona State University, Tempe, Arizona, October 26, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 335)
  - University of Arizona, Tucson, Arizona, October 26, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 336)
  - Press Conference of NAR at the Arizona Inn, Tucson, Arizona, October 26, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 337)
  - Interview of NAR by Betty and Robert Lewis, Tucson, New York, October 26, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 338)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Tucson Trunk 'n Tusk Dinner, Tucson, Arizona, October 26, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 339)
  - TV Taping of NAR on Station KVOA, Tucson, Arizona, October 26, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 340)
  - Press Conference at Hotel Fort Des Moines, Des Moines, Iowa, October 30, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 341)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Iowa Republican State Central Committee Dinner, Des Moines, Iowa, October 30, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 342)
  - Remarks of NAR at the 25th Annual Student Conference on United States Affairs, West Point, New York, October 31, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 343)
  - Family of Man Annual Awards Dinner Honoring Dr. Kissinger, New York Hilton, New York City, November 1, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 344)
  - Swearing in of Howard Shapiro as State Commission of Investigation Chairman, New York City, November 7, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 345)
  - Northeast Regional Council Republican National Committee, Rockefeller Center, New York City, November 13, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 346)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Dedication Ceremonies for the New Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, Rockefeller University, New York City, November 14, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 347)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Foundation Group Luncheon, New York Hilton Hotel, New York City, November 15, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 348)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Academy of Political Science, Columbia University, New York City, November 16, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 349)
  - Press Conference of NAR and Mayor-Elect Abe Beame, New York Subway Fare, New York City, November 20, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 350)
  - NAR at the Dedication of the Empire State Plaza, Albany, New York, November 21, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 351)
  - Remarks of NAR at the State University Trustees Luncheon, 25th Anniversary, State University of New York (SUNY), Albany, New York, November 21, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 352)
  - Remarks of NAR at 5th District Republican Committee Annual Dinner, Minot, North Dakota, November 26, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 353)
  - Remarks of NAR at the 18th District Republican Committee, Grand Forks, North Dakota, November 26, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 354)
  - Remarks of NAR at the University of North Dakota, Grand Forks, North Dakota, November 26, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 355)
  - Press Conference at Grand Forks, North Dakota, November 26, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 356)
  - Press Conference at Minot, North Dakota, November 26, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 357)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Citizens Union Dinner Honoring Alton G. Marshall, New York City, November 27, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 358)
  - Press Conference at 22 West 55th Street, New York City, November 27, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 359)
  - Remarks of NAR at the B'nai B'rith Anti-Defamation League Dinner, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York City, November 29, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 360)
  - Press Questions of NAR after Meeting with Members of congressional Delegation with Mssr. Caso and Beame on Holding the Fare, Washington, D. C., November 30, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 361)
  - News Conference of NAR Following the Morning Session of the National Commission on Critical Choices in America, New York City, December 4, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 362)
  - Press Conference of NAR and Governor-Elect Brendan Byrne (New Jersey), New York City, December 5, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 363)
  - Press Questions of NAR Getting Off the Plane in Atlanta, Georgia, December 7, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 364)
  - Press Conference at Regency Hyatt House, Atlanta, Georgia, December 7, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 365)
  - Remarks of NAR at the 1973 Southern Republican Conference, Atlanta, Georgia, December 7, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 366)
  - Institute of Adult Jewish Studies Dialogue Series, Congregation B'nai Jeshurun, New York City, December 10, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 367)
  - Press Questions of NAR Following Announcement of Resignation in Red Room, State Capital, Albany, New York, December 11, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 368)
  - Press Conference Before "Man of Conscience" Award Dinner, New York City, December 11, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 369)
  - Press Conference of NAR, Lt. Governor Malcolm Wilson and Mayor-Elect Abe Beame, Transit Fare, New York City, December 13, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 370)
  - Press Conference of NAR, Lt. Governor Malcolm Wilson and Mayor-Elect Abe Beame, Transit Fare, New York City, December 14, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 371)
  - Rockefeller Center Press Conference, New York City, January 16, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 372)
  - Governor's Club Dinner-Dance, New York City, January 25, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 373)
  - Washington Press Club Dinner, Washington, D. C., January 29, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 374)
  - Conference of Presidents of Major Jewish Organizations, New York City (Cancelled), January 30, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 375)
  - Travelers Aid Society 1st Annual Awards Dinner Honoring Dr. Ronan, New York City, January 30, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 376)
  - Press Conference of NAR in Denver, Colorado, January 31, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 377)
  - Fossil Fuels Energy Conference, Denver, Colorado, January 31, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 378)
  - Bond Club of New York Annual Dinner, New York City, February 1, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 379)
  - Press Questions of NAR in Rockford, Illinois, February 9, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 380)
  - Remarks of NAR at Rockford, Illinois, February 9, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 381)
  - Interview of NAR on Newsmakers, WREX, Channel 13, Bill Taylor, Rockford, Illinois, February 9, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 382)
  - Fund-Raising Dinner for John Anderson, Rockford, Illinois, February 9, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 383)
  - Remarks of NAR to Cardiologists, New York Hilton, New York City, February 11, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 384)
  - Press Questions of NAR Following Speech to Cardiologists, New York Hilton, New York City, February 11, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 385)
  - Press Conference, 30 Rockefeller Plaza, New York City, February 11, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 386)
  - Republican State Committee of South Dakota, Rapid City, South Dakota, February 12, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 387)
  - Press Conference of NAR in Rapid City, South Dakota, February 12, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 388)
  - Press Conference of NAR in Mitchell, South Dakota, February 12, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 389)
  - Press Conference of NAR in Minneapolis, Minnesota, February 12, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 390)
  - Fund-Raising Luncheon for Senator Robert Dole, Topeka, Kansas, February 13, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 391)
  - Dallas Council on World Affairs, Dallas, Texas, February 21, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 392)
  - Interview of NAR on the Murphy Martin Show, Dallas, Texas, February 21, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 393)
  - Young Republican Leadership Conference, Washington, D. C. (Cancelled), February 28, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 394)
  - Montana Republican Committee Dinner, Billings, Montana, February 28, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 395)
  - Interview of NAR in Route to Billings, Montana, February 28, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 396)
  - Dorchester Conference, Seaside, Oregon, March 1, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 397)
  - NAR at TV Taping, The McKay Show, Seaside, Oregon, March 1, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 398)
  - Remarks of NAR at Testimonial Dinner for Senator Javits, New York Hilton, New York City, March 4, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 399)
  - State University Regents Conference Luncheon, New York Hilton, New York City, March 5, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 400)
  - Pennsylvania Republicans Lincoln Day Dinner, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, March 7, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 401)
  - Sarasota Republican Dinner, Sarasota, Florida, March 8, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 402)
  - 50th Anniversary Luncheon New York Community Trust, The Wall Street Club, New York City, March 8, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 403)
  - Women's National Republican Club Luncheon, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York City (Cancelled), March 9, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 404)
  - Massachusetts Key Republican Club Luncheon, Harvard Club, Boston, Massachusetts, March 13, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 405)
  - Presentation to NAR at the Odyssey House, New York City, March 14, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 406)
  - Legislative Correspondent's Association Dinner, Albany, New York, March 16, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 407)
  - Education and Cultural Fund of the Electrical Industry, Flushing, New York, March 27, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 408)
  - Midwest Republican Leadership Conference, Chicago, Illinois, March 30, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 409)
  - The Inter-American Press Association Luncheon, Miami, Florida, April 3, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 410)
  - TV Interview of NAR at WCKT-News, Miami, Florida, April 3, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 411)
  - Annual Founders' Day, Lincoln, Nebraska, April 6, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 412)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Wharton Graduate Business School Annual Award Dinner, Waldorf-Astoria, New York City, April 16, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 413)
  - Meeting with the Chase Board, New York City, April 17, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 414)
  - Maine Republican State Committee Biennial Convention, Bangor, Maine (Cancelled), April 19, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 415)
  - National Magazine Awards Luncheon, Plaza Hotel, New York City, April 23, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 416)
  - Four Freedoms Foundation Award Dinner, Waldorf-Astoria, New York City, April 25, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 417)
  - NAR and Sol Linowitz on Eternal Light Program on NBC, New York City, April 26, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 418)
  - International Council Chase Bank, New York City (Cancelled), April 30, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 419)
  - Policy Committee Business Roundtable, New York City, May 2, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 420)
  - American Society for Public Administration Convention, Syracuse, New York, May 6, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 421)
  - Jackie Robinson Memorial Award Dinner, New York Hilton, New York City (Cancelled), May 7, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 422)
  - Republican Committee Dinner, Kansas City, Missouri, May 9, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 423)
  - Press Conference of NAR in Little Rock, Arkansas, May 9, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 424)
  - Arkansas Republican State Committee Salute to Winthrop Rockefeller Dinner, Little Rock, Arkansas, May 10, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 425)